(幽鬼丸)フゥ…。
(カブト)さすが 尾獣。
やはり 一筋縄じゃいかないか。
まあいい… 次の手を打つだけさ。
(麟児)ふんっ… ん～っ！
(麟児)おい 無事かい？
(鬼霧)まぁ なんとか。
木ノ葉の連中は
近くにいねえみてえだな。
状況が さっぱりだ。
(鬼霧)なぁ
さっきの大波は何だったんだ？
それに
なんか鳴き声が聞こえたぜ。
紅蓮さんたちは いったい何を？
たぶん
知らねえほうが身のためだな。
おう 牛頭 生きてたか。
(牛頭)あぁ… 紅蓮さんは？
さあな。
(牛頭)お前なら捜せるはずだ。
そうしたいのは山々だが➡
急に コウモリたちの反応が
途絶えちまった。
正直 お手上げだ。
What an impressive Tailed Beast.
The ordinary method
doesn't work, after all.
どこへ行く気だ？
Well, it doesn't matter...
I'll just move on to the next step.
(牛頭)ケガをしているかもしれない。
お前 捜すったって… おい牛頭！
you've gotta be extra careful
mijika ni aru mono
あっ！ チッ…。
with the things nearest to you
tsuneni ki wo tsukete inai to
you know the closer you get to something
amari ni chika sugite
やれやれ お熱なことで。
the tougher it is to see it
miushinatte shimai sou
(ナルト)イテテテ…。
クソッ！ ひでえ目に遭ったってばよ。
いったい どこまで流されたんだ。
explain to me this happiness
anata ga saikin taiken shita
that you just got to experience?
shiawase wa ittai nan desu ka
そうだ！ アイツ…。
or maybe you're so blessed
megumare sugite ite
that you can't even remember it
omoidasenai kamo
なんでアイツ 大蛇丸の仲間なんかと
一緒にいたんだってばよ…。
that you stand here now
ima koko ni iru koto
that you still live and breathe
iki wo shite iru koto
((いいか ソイツに ついて行け。
その手を離すんじゃねえぞ。
I realised that they all were miracles
tada soredake no koto ga
(うん))
just by themselves
kiseki da to kidzuku
you've gotta be extra careful
mijika ni aru mono
もしかして オレのせいで…!?
with the things nearest to you
tsuneni ki wo tsukete inai to
you know the closer you get to something
amari ni chika sugite
クソッ… こんな霧！
the tougher it is to see it
miushinatte shimai sou
you know the closer you get to something
the tougher it is to see it
and i'll never take it for granted
it's fine to say you'll never give up
oi tsudzukete kita yume
and to keep chasing your dreams
akiramezu ni susumeyo nante
but the more time you spend talking big
kirei goto wo ieru hodo
どこだ？ ここ。
the less you get done
nanimo dekicha inai kedo
I will press that handful of courage against my heart
hito nigiri no yuuki wo mune ni
and with its help survive another day
ashita wo ikinuku tame ni
サスケ！
and i'll never take it for granted
(大蛇丸)ジャマしないでちょうだい。
let's go
テメエ！ サスケをどうするつもりだ!?
(大蛇丸)フフフ…。
転生の儀式を始めるのよ。
Inside the Mist
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah... more or less.
It doesn't seem like
the Leaf Ninja are nearby.
But I can't figure out the situation.
何だと!?
(大蛇丸)それが 彼の望み。
Say, what was that huge wave just now?
彼は力を… 私は彼を手に入れる。
And I heard a cry of some sort...
Just what are Guren-san
and the others doing...?
んなことさせっかよ！ サスケは
オレたちの所へ帰ってくるんだ!!
It's probably better for us
if we don't know.
フフフ… バカめ！
彼は そんなこと望んでやしない。
それでも 思ってるヤツがいる所が
帰る場所なんだ！
Oh, Gozu... You're alive.
Yeah... Where's Guren-san?
オレは そう信じてる！
I dunno.
本当に そうかしら。
You should be able to find her!
We'd like nothing better,
but suddenly the bats stopped responding.
うるせえ…。
Frankly, I'm stumped.
Where do you think you're going?
She may be injured...
Hey, finding her is...
Hey Gozu!
Oh, man. He's got a crush on her.
あなた 後悔するわよ。
Owww...
Damn it! I was put through hell.
うるせえ！ とぉ～っ!!
How far down did I wash away?
(カカシ)やめろ ナルト！
(キバ)うわぁ！
I know!
Him...?
フー…。 危ねえ。
What was he doing with
Orochimaru's ally?
カカシ先生。
お前なぁ
せっかく見つけてやったのに➡
Now listen, follow that person!
なんてことしやがんだよ！
でも 今ここに大蛇丸が…。
Don't let that person go!
ああん？
別に何も匂わねえけどな。
Uh-huh...!
That kid...
Could it have been my fault...?!
(カカシ)どうやら 幻覚のようだな。
えっ そんな…。
(赤丸)ワン！ ワン！
Damn it! This fog...!
(ヤマト)大丈夫かい？ ナルト。
(カカシ)無事 全員揃ったな。
(シノ)だが問題がないわけじゃない。
ん？
見てくれ。
これは…。
先ほどから
急に様子が おかしくなった。
Where am I?
方向感覚を やられている。
これでは偵察には使えない。
おい マジかよ!?
この異変は
霧が濃くなってからのようです。
Sasuke?!
(カカシ)こっちも ナルトが幻覚を見た。
どうやら ただの霧じゃないねぇ。
Don't interfere.
Why you--!
What're you gonna do with Sasuke?!
ナルト！ あの湖で何があった？
I'm going to begin
the Reanimation Jutsu.
What...?!
That is his wish.
なんか すんげえ
でっけえカメが暴れてて➡
He will attain power...
And I will attain him.
ソイツと さっきのヤツらが戦ってた。
As if I'd let you!
はぁ？ カメだ!? あのな お前➡
We're gonna take Sasuke
back to our village!
How silly.
He doesn't desire such a thing.
カメが あの でっけえチャクラの
正体だってのかよ!?
うっせえな！ ホントなんだから
しようがねえだろ!!
Still, home is where people
think of you. I believe that...
とにかく さっきの津波は
そのカメが起こしたんだってばよ！
それに アイツを見た ガマ吉のヤツが
三尾だって…。
I wonder if that's true...
Shut up...!
(サクラ)三尾って…
ここに尾獣が出たっていうの!?
You... will regret it.
たぶん… 尻尾の数まで
見たわけじゃねえけど。
Shut up!
Stop! Naruto!
先輩…。
やっと 連中の狙いが
見えてきたと思ったら➡
また とんでもないものを
引き当てたな。
Phew... That was close.
とにかく 一度 この霧の
届かないところまで撤退だ。
Kakashi-sensei...?!
Look, we finally found you.
What do you think you're doing?!
情報を整理して
改めて 今後の策を練る。
Huh?! But Orochimaru was right here...
Huh? I don't pick up any scents.
It seems... that was an illusion.
Huh...? But...
Are you all right, Naruto?
We've assembled everyone.
But it doesn't mean
our problems are over.
Hmm?
Look...
This is...?!
They have started to act weird.
((なぜ 殺さなかったの？))
Their sense of direction is shot.
We can't use them for reconnaissance.
Hey, hey, are you serious...?
It started after the fog became thicker.
On our side, Naruto saw an illusion.
It seems this is no ordinary fog.
Naruto... What happened at that lake?
Huh?
There was... this giant rampaging turtle.
Those guys we fought earlier
were fighting it.
Hmm?
What...? A turtle...?!
Hey... are you saying that
giant Chakra was actually a turtle?
《紅蓮 : なんだ？ 今のは…》
紅蓮さん…！
Shut up! I'm telling the truth!
幽鬼丸…。
Anyway, the turtle caused
that giant wave!
《そうか
私は 三尾と やりあって➡
Gamakichi saw that thing and
said it was a Three-Tails...
意識をなくしてたのか…。
しかし 三尾の力が
これほどまでとは…。
Three-Tails...?!
A Tailed Beast appeared here?
おそらく 他の連中も
あの激流に巻き込まれたか。
Probably... Although it's not like
he saw how many tails he had...
木ノ葉が動いているとなると➡
Senpai...
早いとこ 麟児たちと
合流しておきたいところだが➡
Just when I thought we figured out
their target...
この霧では…》
We've come across
another puzzling thing...
三尾のほうは どうなった？
わからない。
In any case, we must retreat to
somewhere this fog can't reach us.
We'll go through all our data
and plan our next strategy.
あれから静かになっちゃったし。
そうか。
でも よかった。
紅蓮さんの目が覚めて。
ずっと うなされてたんだよ。
いくら呼んでも
全然起きてくれなくて。
《そうか…。
コイツ 私が倒れてる間 ずっと…》
Why didn't you kill him?
What was that just now...?
Guren-san...
Yuukimaru...?
I see... I fought with a Three-Tails
and lost consciousness.
I never imagined that the Three-Tails
would have such power...
That raging current probably
swallowed up the rest.
If the Hidden Leaf are on the move,
I want to join up with Rinji
and the others, but in this fog...
じゃあ
とっとと他のヤツらを捜すか。
What happened to the Three-Tails?
うん でも どうかな…。
なんだ？
I don't know...
It suddenly got quiet...
なんだか ヘンなんだ。
体に力が入らなくて…。
I see...
But I'm glad. That you woke up...
お前 また熱が！ いつから？
You were moaning the whole time...
You wouldn't wake up,
no matter how many times
I called out your name...
I get it...
He stayed by me
the whole time I was unconscious...
Now then. Shall we go find the others?
(ヒナタ)白眼！
Uh-huh. But I wonder...
What?
It's sorta strange.
I don't have any strength in my body...
すごい！
(サイ)何か わかりましたか？
えぇ 戻りましょう。
You have a fever again!
Since when...?
(サイ)はい。
(カカシ)どうだった？
(ヒナタ)はい 確かにあれは
ただの霧じゃありません。
中には かなりのチャクラが
含まれています。
Byakugan!
しかも 湖を
まるごと包み込んでいる➡
かなりのチャクラ量です。
Oh! Amazing...!
霧は 三尾が
発生させているとみて➡
Did you see something?
間違いなさそうですね。
そうだな。
Yes. Let's go back.
All right...
ナルトの話からすると あの霧には
幻覚を見せる力があるようだ。
ある種の
結界のようなものだろう。
How did it go?
湖に近づくのは 危険ですね。
Yes... That is surely no ordinary fog.
まずいってばよ！
あの中に まだアイツが！
There's quite a bit of Chakra
inside it.
(キバ)アイツって？
サクラちゃん ほら 覚えてんだろ？
Furthermore, it has totally
enveloped the lake.
It's a considerable amount of Chakra.
ここに来る途中 オレが
知り合いに会ったって言ったこと。
I guess we're right to conclude that
the fog was produced by the Three-Tails.
そういえば。
あぁ ナルトの妄想の。
Yes...
って 失礼なこと言うな！
According to what Naruto said,
とにかく ソイツが湖に…➡
that fog has the power to
make you hallucinate.
この霧の中にいるんだってばよ！
It's like a kind of barrier.
湖にね…。
頼む カカシ先生➡
It's dangerous to approach the lake.
アイツは 忍者じゃねえんだ。
That's bad!
He's still inside there...!
無事かどうか
確かめに行かせてくれ。
He...?
残念だが ナルト 許可はできない。
カカシ先生！
Remember Sakura-chan, I told you before.
I met him on the way here.
お前 さっき
三尾の幻覚にやられ➡
Oh, that's right...
もう少しで 同士討ちになるところ
だっただろう➡
Oh, when you were delirious...
単独行動は 論外だ。
Quit being so rude!
Anyway, he's still on the lake!
それは そうだけどよ。
Inside the fog...!
でもよ カカシ先生➡
The lake?
実際問題
これから どうするんだ？
Please, Kakashi-sensei!
He's not a Ninja!
なりゆきとはいえ 大蛇丸の
アジトの探索からは➡
I have to find out if he's okay...
ずいぶん かけ離れちまったよな。
Sorry, Naruto. I can't allow it...
まぁ 事が
ここまで大きくなると➡
Kakashi-sensei!
Earlier, you were ensnared
by the Three-Tails' illusion
さすがに オレが勝手に
判断していい問題じゃない。
and almost ended up killing
your comrade.
ってことで すでに パックンを
木ノ葉に走らせてある。
Acting on your own
is out of the question.
綱手様の指示が来るまで
オレたちは ここで待機だ。
I... I know that, but...
But Kakashi-sensei...
The problem is... what'll we do now?
(カカシ)しばらくは 霧の外側から
連中と三尾の動きを監視する。
Whatever has developed,
we've fallen far off track from
searching for Orochimaru's hideout.
いいな。
はい。
(パックン)ということじゃ。
Well, the situation has gotten too big
for me to make arbitrary decisions.
(綱手)三尾は 先の大戦のなか➡
行方知れずになったと
聞いていたが➡
And so, I've already sent Pakkun
back to Hidden Leaf Village.
こんな形で現れるとは。
We'll wait here until we get orders
from Tsunade-sama.
(パックン)大蛇丸のヤツ➡
やっかいなものに
手を出しおったもんじゃ。
In the meantime, stay outside
the perimeter of the fog
(シズネ)ですが 尾獣は 暁が
血眼になって探しているはず➡
and keep an eye on
the Three-Tails and those others.
Understood?
我々が 先に発見できたのは
不幸中の幸いかもしれません。
- Yes!
そうだな。
このうえ 暁の耳に入れば➡
三つ巴の
泥仕合になることは確実。
That's the gist of it.
I had heard that the Three-Tails
disappeared after the last Great War.
But to have it reappear in this form...
Orochimaru has gotten involved
in something troubling.
But the Akatsuki are desperately
searching for Tailed Beasts.
Perhaps the fact that we discovered it
first is a blessing in disguise.
誰にも 渡すわけにはいかない。
では 捕獲を？
Yes... But if the Akatsuki get wind of this,
容易ではなさそうだがな。
it's certain to turn into tug-of-war
for the Three-Tails.
(綱手)しかし 前例がない
というわけでもあるまい。
We cannot hand it over to anyone.
You'll capture it then?
私は 過去の文献をあたる。
I don't think it will be easy...
However, there must be
some kind of precedent...
お前は その間に
そこに書いてあるメンバーを招集しろ。
了解しました。
I'm going to look it up in
our existing documents.
I want you to summon
the members I've written there.
Understood!
(いの)フゥ～ 終わった。
今日は あなたが来てくれて
助かったわ。
ホントですか？
ええ これからも がんばってね。
はい！
All done...
Thank you for your help today.
Really...?!
Yes... Please keep up the good work.
(テンテン)ハァ ハァ これ以上はムリよ。
Yes!
これからですよ テンテン。
(リー)これからが 本当の勝負です。
(ガイ)よく言ったぞ リー。 ハッハッ。
I can't go on...
青春に弱音は禁物だ テンテン。
We're just beginning, Tenten.
The real challenge begins now!
そうですよ。 仲間とは 常に
お互いを意識し➡
Well said, Lee!
その背中を守り合うもの。
Words of weakness in the midst
of your youth are forbidden, Tenten!
お互い 体術を極めた者同士➡
Right!
無敵のコンビネーションを
手に入れようじゃありませんか。
To be mutually aware of one's partner
and to watch each other's back!
だから アンタのスタンドプレーに
振り回されて➡
To hone one's skills in Taijutsu
to form an unbeatable combination.
疲れが倍化してんのよ。
ウム リーよ。 この修業の目的は何だ？
Let us do that!
And trying to keep up with
all your showboating is wearing me out!
味方同士の連携。
Hmm?! Lee, what is the purpose
of this training?
つまり あうんの呼吸を
つかみ合う修業… です。
Huh?
そうだ。 だが 今 お前は
テンテンと呼吸が合ってると思うか？
Coordination with one's partners.
It's training to build up synergy!
あっ。
(テンテン)ハァ ハァ…。
Correct!
However, do you think you are
in harmony with Tenten right now?
《息が荒い。 しまった》
わかりました ガイ先生。
ボクの気持が先走りすぎたようです。
She's breathing hard... Oh no!
さすがオレの教え子だ。
のみ込みが早い。
I understand, Sensei.
It seems my feelings have
gotten ahead of hers.
だいたい こんな調子で
５時間ぶっ続けじゃ➡
That's my student!
You catch on quickly!
いくつ体があっても
もたないわよ。
ボクは まだまだやれますよ。
(ガイ)よく言った リーよ。
Cripes, we've been at this nonstop
for five hours.
No matter how many bodies I have,
I can't hold up.
では テンテンの息が整い次第
修業再開だ。
I still have a lot left in me!
オレの体術で
容赦なく攻撃するから➡
Well said, Lee!
As soon as Tenten has caught her breath,
we'll resume training!
全力で回避し受け止めてみせろ。
I'm going to perform a Taijutsu attack
without holding back,
オッス ガイ先生！
えぇ～。
so counter me with all your might!
《ハァ 結局まだやるのか》
Right, Guy-sensei!
(テンテン)ちょっと待って あれ。
We're going to continue anyway...?
(リー)招集… ですか？
Wait, look...!
(ガイ)よし 続きは帰ってからだ。
いってこい ２人とも。
We're being called up?
熱き血潮をたぎらせて
修業の成果を見せつけてやれ！
All right.
We'll continue after you get back!
Go, you two! Show them the results
of your long, arduous training!
オッス。
はい。
と まあ おおまかな説明は以上だ。
- Right!
- Yes!
(綱手)これより お前たちには➡
And that's the gist of the situation.
先に出発したカカシたちの
サポートに回ってもらう。
You will go to support Kakashi
and the others
わかっていると思うが 最優先
なのは三尾を封印することだ。
who have gone ahead of you.
You are probably aware by now
(シズネ)封印には繊細な
チャクラコントロールが必要になるわ。
that the most critical thing is
to seal the Three-Tails.
Sealing the Three-Tails will require
extremely delicate Chakra control.
医療忍者である 私と いの。
現地にいるサクラとヒナタで
封印班を組む予定よ。
Medical Ninja consisting
of myself and Ino;
plus Sakura and Hinata,
who are already there,
はい がんばります。
will form the Sealing unit.
リーとテンテンには ヒナタとサクラが
抜けた穴を埋めてもらいたい。
Right! I'll do my best!
Lee and Tenten,
I need you to fill the gap
that Hinata and Sakura will be leaving.
敵が三尾を狙っている以上
戦闘は避けられんだろうからな。
As long as the enemy is after
the Three-Tails,
任せてください。
青春フルパワーで戦ってみせますよ。
confrontation will be inevitable.
You can count on us!
We'll fight with the full power
of our youth!
現地までは ワシが案内する。
I will lead you to the site.
Don't lag behind!
皆 遅れるなよ！
《ったく 他人の看病して 自分が
倒れちゃ 話にならないだろ》
Geez, it won't do if you collapse
from nursing the sick.
《コイツの面倒を見るのは
２回目だな》
This is my second time
taking care of him...
((紅蓮 : そんな量を飲ませたら…))
If you give him that much medicine...
《もしかしたら
あの薬のせいなのか？》
Could those pills be the cause...?
《とにかく コイツを連れて➡
In any case, I must avoid a battle
with the enemy while I have him.
敵と戦闘になるようなことは
避けないと》
ゴホッ ゴホゴホッ。
おい 幽鬼丸 しっかりしろ！
Hey, Yuukimaru. Wake up.
あの… ね…➡
You know...
The place I can return to... is by you.
紅蓮さんが…
ボクの帰る場所… なんだ…。
えっ？
Huh?
やっと… 見つけた…。
I finally... found it.
We're supposed to be on watch
until the next shift. That Naruto!
《もう… みんな 交代で
見張りしてるっていうのに➡
ナルトのヤツ！》
Don't slack off.
何さぼってんのよ。
Huh?
Sakura... I've been thinking...
サクラちゃん…。
オレ… ずっと考えてたんだ…。
Huh?
But I can't find an answer by myself.
けど… １人じゃ
答えが見つからなくて…。
Back then, when I was training...
the Pervy Sage said something to me.
この間 修業の時…➡
Jiraiya-sama?
エロ仙人が言ってたんだ…。
自来也様が？
"Wherever someone thinks of you,
that's where home is."
「思っている人がいるところが
帰る場所」なんだって…。
That's a nice saying.
ステキな言葉…。
But... is that really true?
それって… ホントに
そうなのかな… って…。
If that's true, then if we keep
thinking about someone,
that person would return, right?
もし そうなら
こっちが思い続ければ➡
ソイツは帰ってくるってことだろ…。
Yes... I'd like to think that.
そうね… そうであってほしい
と思うけど…。
But no matter how much
we think of someone,
there are some who won't return.
どんなに思ってたって…
帰ってこない人はいる…。
It's a very difficult thing...
to have your thoughts reach someone.
思いを伝えるのって…
すごく難しいことだよね…。
Yet, if you give up... and there's no one
to think about that person...
だからって… 伝えることを
あきらめちまったら…。
That's sad.
思ってくれる人が
いなくなったら…。
Yes. If we give up, then there really
won't be a place to return to.
つれえよな…。
確かに… 私たちが
あきらめちゃったら…。
Yes!
No matter what anyone says,
we just have to keep thinking of him...
本当に帰る場所が
なくなっちゃうものね。
そうよ！ 誰がなんと言おうと➡
and create a place where
he can return freely at any time.
私たちが思い続けることで…➡
Sakura-chan...
いつでも気楽に帰れる場所を
作っておかなくちゃ！
Okay?
You're right.
We just can't give up. Right!
サクラちゃん…。
…なんてね。
そうだよな…。 やっぱ オレたちが➡
I feel much better,
thanks to you, Sakura-chan!
あきらめるわけには
いかねえよな… うん！
I'm going back to my position.
サクラちゃんのおかげで
すっきりしたってばよ！
In thirty minutes,
the next two-man team will relieve us.
じゃ 私 そろそろ持ち場に戻る。
So stay alert.
30分もしたら
次のツーマンセルが交代に来るから➡
Thank you! Sakura-chan...
She's right...
So if someone is thinking about me,
then that's the place I go back to?
Yup... No matter what anyone says,
just keep thinking about him.
But... if he really has no place to go...
I'll be the one he can come home to.
Oh my god! Oh my god!
oh my god oh my god
yesterday's mistake got me discouraged, but
kinou no shippai de kojiketatte
Thank you! Thank you!
gottsuanda gottsuanda
my new clothes got splashed with some sauce, wow
onyuu no fuku ni sousu ga hanete wao
don't mind, don't mind, if I stay feeling like this I'll have a tear in my eyes
donmai donmai shizunda mama ja namida mo my eyes
I may be hungry and angry
donna ni hangurii de angurii demo
but I'll grab a bowl to eat and start dancing!
donburi kutte danshingu
We'll always be pals my brother!
orera itsumo demo nakama daro burazaa
hit me with an upwind or strong wind or a storm I'm ready so come on!
tatoe gyarufuu kyoufuu arashi ga fuitemo bacchikoi kamon
we may be apart but we'll still be under the same sky
hanaretetemo onaji sora no shita de
so smile and hang on
saa waratte funbatte
lets do it do it do it do it
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
even if morning doesn't come, yay yay
tatoe asa ga konakutatte yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
we'll still watch the dream together, yay yay
kimi to tomo ni yume wo miru ze yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
no matter what, don't ever, ever give up, yay yay
nani ga nandemo aa demo kou demo akirameru na yay yay
Bring it, bring it baby!
bacchikoi bacchikoi baby
morning will always come after night, yay yay
donna yoru mo asa wa kuru ze yay yay
nanananana
アンタも しっかり見張りなさいよ。
Next Episode
Sakura, I'm here to relieve you.
サンキュー… サクラちゃん。
Right. So far,
there's been nothing unusual.
Um... Excuse me...
What's wrong, Sai?
Your position is over there.
そうだよな…。
Well, I don't see Naruto.
((じゃあ 誰かが
ボクのことを思ってくれたら➡
What?! Did that guy go back without
having anybody take over his position?!
(そこが ボクの
帰る場所になるんだね))
If so, we would've crossed paths...
《そうだ… 誰が なんと言おうと
思い続ければいい》
We're talking Naruto here.
He may just be sleeping somewhere.
No way... That Naruto...
Everyone's Feelings
《でもって…
アイツが本当に帰る場所…➡
Next time: "Everyone's Feelings"
ないんなら…
オレが帰る場所になってやる！》